HIMANSHU PANDEY

Space & Interior Design



CONTACT

- **(** 9667935969, 9918743130
- pandeyh061@gmail.com
- Be behance.net/himanshupandey3
- in linkedin.com/in/pandey-hp

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Deisgn The Design Village, Noida, 2018-2022

Higher Senior Secondary School

Saraswati Vidya Mandir Senior Secondary School, 2017

SOFTWARE SKILLS

















SKILLS

Design process and thinking, sketching, rendering, Research, story-boarding, interior designing, space planning, team work, creative thinking

LANGAUGE

Hindi, English, Bhojpuri

PROFILE

Being a part of spatial design, I am always oriented towards hands-on experience which lies between, Public space design, construction process, furniture design, and conceptual design, which leads to devolop my focus towards context based deisgn, and that is why I am considered myself as a contextual designer.

EXPERIENCE

Interior Design-Intern Florence Design Studio (March 2021- May 2021)

- Client meeting, client presentation
- 2d- Drawing- Wall elevation, floor plan, celing plan, electrical plan, furniture layout
- Site visit
- Discuss with team lead about ongoing project

Interior Design- Intern Divyakash Atelier(May 2021- July 2021)

- Client meeting, client presentation
- 2d- Drawing- Wall elevation, floor plan, ceiling plan, furniture layout